Hold me tight.
أمسك بي بقوة.
Is Lin Mojiao crazy?
هل لين موجياو مجنونة؟
He's always been a lunatic.
لقد كان مجنوناً منذ البداية.
There's nothing in this remote area.
لا يوجد شيء في هذه المنطقة النائية.
What do we do now?
ماذا نفعل الآن؟
Follow me.
اتبعني.
Don't touch me.
لا تلمسني.
These two are delicious.
هذان الاثنان لذيذان.
This starfruit and the wax apple
فاكهة النجمة وتفاحة الشمع
are very good. This doesn't look authentic.
جيدة جداً. هذا لا يبدو أصلياً.
It's authentic.
إنه أصلي.
You talk as if
تتحدث كما لو
you are familiar with this place.
أنت على دراية بهذا المكان.
Buy, buy, buy. Have a taste.
اشترِ، اشترِ، اشترِ. جرّب.
It's delicious.
إنه لذيذ.
It's tastier than the dipped one.
إنها ألذ من تلك المغموسة.
Have a taste.
تذوقها.
It's okay if you don't buy.
لا بأس إن لم تشترِ.
I'm hungry. I want to eat.
أنا جائع. أريد أن آكل.
You try it.
جربها بنفسك.
It's not fresh.
إنه ليس طازجاً.
If you want to eat seafood,
إذا كنت ترغب في تناول المأكولات البحرية،
you should go to the seaside.
يجب أن تذهب إلى شاطئ البحر.
We don't have money.
ليس لدينا مال.
I'm tired and hungry now.
أنا متعب وجائع الآن.
Where are you taking me?
إلى أين تأخذني؟
We'll be there soon.
سنكون هناك قريباً.
Come on.
تعال.
Why did he come here?
لماذا أتى إلى هنا؟
What is this place?
ما هذا المكان؟
Dad,
أب،
Mom,
أم،
I'll send my brother to see you soon.
سأرسل أخي لرؤيتك قريباً.
I almost forgot.
كادت أن تفوتني.
I also prepared a daughter-in-law for you.
لقد جهزت لك زوجة ابن أيضاً.
You will be very happy.
ستكون سعيدًا جدًا.
Can I borrow your necklace?
هل يمكنني استعارة قلادتك؟
Can you do it?
هل يمكنك فعل ذلك؟
Use this as collateral.
استخدم هذا كضمان.
One thousand.
ألف.
Five hundred.
خمسمائة.
Place your bets.
ضع رهاناتك.
Please look at the cards.
يرجى الاطلاع على البطاقات.
[Place your bets.]
[ضع رهاناتك.]
Bet you don't have a King.
أراهن أن ليس لديك ملك.
Straight flush wins.
يفوز ستريت فلاش.
Boss,
رئيس،
someone deliberately disrupted the casino's rules.
قام شخص ما بتعطيل قواعد الكازينو عمداً.
Maybe they're here to cause trouble. Old rules.
ربما هم هنا لإثارة المشاكل. قواعد قديمة.
Yes.
نعم.
Enough. Time to go.
كفى. حان وقت الرحيل.
Leaving already?
هل ستغادر بالفعل؟
They're running back.
إنهم يركضون للخلف.
Stop!
قف!
Don't run!
لا تركض!
You guys go over there. Okay.
اذهبوا إلى هناك. حسناً.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
You're shy.
أنت خجول.
I'm hungry. Let's go eat.
أنا جائع. هيا بنا نأكل.
I'll show you around.
سأريك المكان.
That looks good. I want to eat that.
يبدو شهياً. أريد أن آكله.
How
كيف
How to play this?
كيف تلعب هذه اللعبة؟
Take this ball
خذ هذه الكرة
to hit that board.
للوصول إلى تلك اللوحة.
Then these two boys will fall into the water.
ثم سيسقط هذان الصبيان في الماء.
I want to play.
أريد أن ألعب.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Yes, try that.
نعم، جرب ذلك.
I'll give you a doll.
سأعطيك دمية.
It's so ugly. I don't want it.
إنه قبيح للغاية. لا أريده.
It's not ugly.
إنه ليس قبيحاً.
Look, this doll is so much like you.
انظري، هذه الدمية تشبهك كثيراً.
Annoying.
مزعج.
You seem to know this place very well.
يبدو أنك تعرف هذا المكان جيداً.
Many people know that
يعلم الكثير من الناس ذلك
the second son of the Lin family is abroad.
الابن الثاني لعائلة لين موجود في الخارج.
But no one cares
لكن لا أحد يهتم
why I stay abroad.
لماذا أبقى في الخارج؟
After my father died,
بعد وفاة والدي،
Lin Mojiao was very concerned about me,
كانت لين موجياو قلقة للغاية عليّ،
chasing me all the way abroad.
يلاحقني في جميع أنحاء البلاد.
He also taught me a lot of survival skills.
كما علمني الكثير من مهارات البقاء على قيد الحياة.
Where did this little brat run off to?
إلى أين هرب هذا الطفل المزعج؟
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
A kid that young fell into the sea.
طفل صغير سقط في البحر.
He must be dead.
لا بد أنه مات.
Let's go. Go, go, go.
هيا بنا. انطلق، انطلق، انطلق.
One.
واحد.
Two.
اثنين.
Three.
ثلاثة.
Four.
أربعة.
Five.
خمسة.
Six.
ستة.
Seven.
سبعة.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I didn't know you went through all this.
لم أكن أعلم أنك مررت بكل هذا.
I thought you hated him
ظننت أنك تكرهه
just for fighting over the inheritance.
لمجرد النزاع على الميراث.
Turns out,
اتضح،
what he did to you
ما فعله بك
was even worse than I imagined.
كان الأمر أسوأ مما تخيلت.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
none of this matters.
لا شيء من هذا يهم.
After all,
في النهاية،
I made all this
لقد صنعت كل هذا
up.
أعلى.
You're so naive.
أنت ساذج جداً.
You actually believe that?
هل تصدق ذلك حقاً؟
Were you feeling sorry for me just now?
هل كنت تشعر بالشفقة عليّ الآن؟
Have you ever heard a saying?
هل سبق لك أن سمعت قولاً مأثوراً؟
What?
ماذا؟
Feeling sorry for a man
الشعور بالشفقة على رجل
is the beginning of misfortune.
إنها بداية المصائب.
Why did you buy a cake?
لماذا اشتريت كعكة؟
I just saw it. It's not bad.
لقد شاهدته للتو. إنه ليس سيئاً.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You gave me the whole set.
لقد أعطيتني المجموعة كاملة.
Don't waste it. Make a wish.
لا تضيعها. تمنَّ أمنية.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Happy birthday.
عيد ميلاد سعيد.